{
	"questions": [
		{
			"question": "What is PHP mainly used for?",
			"answer1": "Web development",
			"answer2": "Game development",
			"answer3": "Mobile app development",
			"answer4": "Data analysis",
			"correct": "Web development"
		},
		{
			"question": "All variables in PHP start with which symbol?",
			"answer1": "&",
			"answer2": "%",
			"answer3": "_",
			"answer4": "$",
			"correct": "$"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following is NOT a way to end a PHP statement?",
			"answer1": ";",
			"answer2": ".",
			"answer3": "!",
			"answer4": "None of the above",
			"correct": "."
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the correct way to access the third element in an array?",
			"answer1": "$array[2]",
			"answer2": "$array[3]",
			"answer3": "$array(2)",
			"answer4": "$array(3)",
			"correct": "$array[2]"
		},
		{
			"question": "What function is used to output text in PHP?",
			"answer1": "echo",
			"answer2": "print",
			"answer3": "output",
			"answer4": "display",
			"correct": "echo"
		},
		{
			"question": "Object-oriented programming is a style of programming where you organize your program around ___ rather than ___ and data rather than logic.",
			"answer1": "functions; actions",
			"answer2": "objects; actions",
			"answer3": "actions; functions",
			"answer4": "actions; objects",
			"correct": "objects; actions"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which is the correct format for adding a comment to a PHP script?",
			"answer1": "all of these answers",
			"answer2": "#This is a comment",
			"answer3": "/* This is a comment */",
			"answer4": "// This is a comment",
			"correct": "all of these answers"
		},
		{
			"question": "You want to list the modules available in your PHP installation. What command should you run?",
			"answer1": "php -h",
			"answer2": "php info",
			"answer3": "php -v",
			"answer4": "php -m",
			"correct": "php -m"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the value of $result in this calculation? $result = 25 % 6;",
			"answer1": "1",
			"answer2": "4",
			"answer3": "1.5",
			"answer4": "4.167",
			"correct": "1"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which PHP variable name is invalid?",
			"answer1": "$Double",
			"answer2": "$double",
			"answer3": "$_2times",
			"answer4": "$2times",
			"correct": "$2times"
		}
	]
}